module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What vitamin is produced when a person is exposed to sunlight?', 
    a: 'Vitamin A',
    b: 'Vitamin B',
    c: 'Vitamin C',
    d: 'Vitamin D',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is a keyboard instrument?', 
    a: 'Theracord',
    b: 'Ripcord',
    c: 'Sashcord',
    d: 'Harpsichord',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is a weight category in professional boxing?', 
    a: 'Welterweight',
    b: 'Weebloweight',
    c: 'Slaughterweight',
    d: 'Braithwaite',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which group of Native American people primarily reside in the Southwestern United States?', 
    a: 'Sioux',
    b: 'Cherokee',
    c: 'Navajo',
    d: 'Shoshone',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of disc could be written to, erased, and written to again?', 
    a: 'CD-ROM',
    b: 'CD-R',
    c: 'CD-RW',
    d: 'CD-8x',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the main villain in the animated TV show "The Thundercats"?', 
    a: 'Fat Cat',
    b: 'Mumm-Ra',
    c: 'Skeletor',
    d: 'Panthro',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is rioja a type of?', 
    a: 'Vegetable',
    b: 'Garment',
    c: 'Wine',
    d: 'Fruit',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these things is roughly the same size and shape as your appendix?', 
    a: 'Penny',
    b: 'Bowling Ball',
    c: 'Finger',
    d: 'Onion',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Whose ear did Mike Tyson bite off in 1997?', 
    a: 'Evander Holyfield',
    b: 'Lennox Lewis',
    c: 'Joe Frazier',
    d: 'George Foreman',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'The 1970s TV show "Taxi" helped launch the career of which actor/actress?', 
    a: 'Rhea Pearlman',
    b: 'Ted Danson',
    c: 'Danny DeVito',
    d: 'Woody Harrelson',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];